https://checkwriter.net/privacy-policy.html

ORDER BLANK CHECKSUPGRADE TO CLOUDCLOUD LOGIN
Search for:
FAQ’sChecks By PhoneChecks By FaxTake Checks OnlineCheck DraftFree DemoORDEROrder CheckWriter™Upgrade CheckWriter™Blank Check StockABOUT USGet InfoSUPPORTTRACK ORDER Call toll free 1-800-893-6001Official Privacy PolicyDue to the fact that Boston Commerce, Inc. and yourfavorite.com, and its affiliates, routinely gather sensitive personal and business information from its web-sites, we have established an official privacy policy to protect our customers.All information gathered at Boston Commerce, Inc., owned sites containing personal or sensitive payment information is intended to be gathered using a secure, and encrypted method of submission. If information is not being gathered securely at our website, http:// rather than https:// will  appear in the URL.No sensitive information such as credit card numbers, checking account information, business tax ID numbers and the like will be knowingly transmitted via methods deemed as insecure by Bosotn Commerce, Inc. or yourfavorite.com staff. Yourfavorite.com does not reject receipt of insecure sensitive data, via email, support ticket system or other methods.Regarding personal contact information, Boston Commerce, Inc. and yourfavorite.com will never sell, lease, distribute, or otherwise disclose the name, address, company name, phone, or any other contact information such as eMail address, mailing address, or fax number, to any other party not directly related to, affiliated with, or owned by Boston Commerce, Inc. or  yourfavorite.com in Boston without proper consent, or legal mandate.All CheckWriter™ Cloud and BetterCheck™ accounts are run as Virtual Terminal Software, and Boston Commerce, Inc. and yourfavorite.com employees do not have direct access to encrypted account data, log in, or customer’s client payment information stored in these private virtual terminal environments beyond user’s identity and card on file information for recurring billing. Boston Commerce, Inc., and  yourfavorite.com will not supply customer identity information to any non-affiliated third party without a valid subpoena.If you supply your email address, fax number or mailing address, Boston Commerce, Inc., yourfavorite.com and/or its affiliates may send you email announcements, mailers, or faxes regarding promotions or other events, including, but not limited to special offers and changes with your account.  These announcements will be bound by our terms of service and acceptable uses policy and the submission of your address and name will constitute agreement with these terms when the term of service are posted at point of submission. We will not sell your contact information or personal data to any third party not affiliated with Boston Commerce, Inc., or yourfavorite.com.IF YOU EVER FEEL YOUR PRIVACY HAS BEEN COMPROMISED – please, report it to us immediately, so we may investigate and take the appropriate action.We take our customer data and contact information very seriously. We are in the business of secure information transfer, and welcome any and all suggestions and reports of foul play with regard to client security and privacy.If you need to contact us regarding the above privacy policy, you may call toll free 1-800-893-6001 and speak with a manager on duty. Or if you prefer you may open a support ticket at http://yourfavorite.com/help, or write to us snail mail to 119 Braintree Street, Suite 510, Boston, MA 02134.Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.Should your privacy be compromised through a known breach in security, you will be sent notice to your email address on file that such a breach occurred.Search
Search for:
Latest news All Products Now Plug-in to CheckWriter™ + New API eCheck Direct Customers Welcome – “e Check Direct is Not Answering the Phone” Welcome Cyber Chex Customers: Cyber-Chex to Close May 31, 2020 WebDebit™ Collects the Payment: Use Invoice / API or Plug-In Text-a-Check™ – Get a verified check from your customer
Legacy Edition on CD or Flash
No Longer Legal to Use, the CheckWriter™ Legacy Editions 1.1 to 7.9 are
No longer supported.×Upgrade to comply with:- EPC-6 Federal Reserve Regulation
- PCI / DSS Standards
- US Data Security LawsRead More
